good morning.
おはよう
Akari-chan, it's been a while.
あかりちゃん、久々だね
Well, I'm sure Rory is still a public relations person. Is it a public relations thing?
ね、相変わらず 広報なロリーでお間違いない 広報ですか?
Yeah.
うん
Isn't it non-public relations?
非広報じゃない?
Today, wait a minute, lend me that for a second.
今日のさ、ちょっと待って、ちょっとそれ貸して
Today's, eh?
今日のさ、え?
Is today's outfit coverable?
今日の服装 かばくない?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
It's cute though.
かわいいんだけど
Wait, do you always wear clothes like that?
え、あんな服装いつも着てんの?
What's up below?
下どうなん?
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃかわいいじゃん
why?
なんで?
Don't touch my boobs.
おっぱい触んないで
Why are breasts no good?
なんでおっぱいダメなの?
I'll touch it.
触っちゃう
Why not?
なんでダメなの?
Miscellaneous?
雑い?
sorry.
ごめん
Uncle was busy, then.
おじさん雑かったわ、じゃあ
I'm sorry.
ご めんね
18 years old?
18歳?
18 years old is, oh, okay.
18歳はさ、 あ、いいよ
sorry.
ごめん
You can sit down.
座っていいよ
How was it when you were 18 years old?
この間さ、18歳どうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
it was fun?
楽しかった?
Was it fun to shoot during this time?
この間の撮影楽しかった?
Yeah.
うん
So will I meet this old man again?
だからまたこんなおじさんと会っちゃうの?
Yeah.
うん
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
Akane-chan is a good girl.
あかねちゃん、いい子だね
He's such a nice kid.
めちゃくちゃいい子だね
With such a cute face, such a body,
こんなかわいい顔して、 こんな体して、
Will you meet your uncle again?
またおじさんと会ってくれるの?
Yeah.
うん
That's why I'm so happy to meet you, uncle.
おじさんさ、だからさ、会うのうれしすぎてさ、
I have a little surprise present for you.
ちょっとサプライズでプレゼントあるんだけど
good?
いい?
I prepared a present for you today.
プレゼント今日用意したんだよね
Today I'm giving you a present called Chin Chin,
今日チンチンっていうプレゼントをさ、
How many?
何本かな?
I've prepared a few books for you.
何本か用意させてもらったんだけど
Do you have experience?
経験ある?
do not have.
ない
There isn't.
ないよね
That's one on one, right?
1対1があれでしょ?
There is only one.
しかないよね
Yeah.
うん
hey.
ね
Well, that's true.
ま、そりゃそうだよね
Today, even in the middle of all this, there are so many things going on.
今日さ、そんな中でもさ、 いろいろおチンチンさ、
I prepared a little bit, so there are probably quite a few cocks I've never seen before.
ちょっと用意したからさ、 たぶん見たことないおチンチンも結構
I think so, so I hope you enjoy it.
ある と思うから、 楽しんでくれたらなと思うんだけどさ、
Are you interested?
興味ある?
be.
ある
Is there one?
あるの?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, it's so cute.
え、めっちゃかわいいじゃん
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
You're 18 years old, you're interested, right?
18歳で、興味あるんでしょ?
Cock.
おチンチン
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃかわいいじゃん
With this beauty, with this face, with this glossy skin,
この美しで、 この顔で、 この肌ツヤで、
That's too bad.
やばすぎだろ
This might be the thumbnail.
これ サムネかもか
It was a duality repice.
デュアティレピースでした
Can you measure it?
測ってくれるかな?
this.
これ
I just turned 18.
18歳になってんだけどさ
I'm sorry, but in my uncle's eyes, I'm 15 years old.
ごめんだけど、おじさんの目には15歳、
I only look like a 16 year old.
16歳にしか見えないんだけど
It's just public relations.
ちゃんと広報でーすってね
Well then, I think it's time to give you a present.
じゃあ、そろそろプレゼントあげちゃおうかな
want?
欲しい?
present.
プレゼント
want.
欲しい
want?
欲しい?
Do you want it?
欲しいの?
It was fun during this time.
この間さ、楽しかったじゃん
What did you enjoy most?
何が一番楽しかった?
Did it feel good?
気持ちかった?
It felt good.
気持ちかった
That's right.
そうだよね
Akane-chan is definitely an M.
アカネちゃんやっぱMだもんね
Well then, let's have a lot of fun today.
じゃあいっぱい、今日は楽しんでもらおうか
Well then, let's get together for a moment.
じゃあちょっと、集まってもらおうか
Are you surprised?
びっくりする?
Are you a little nervous?
ちょっと緊張する?
do.
する
do?
する?
Really?
本当に?
I don't feel like I'm nervous though.
なんか緊張してる感じしないけど
Do you want to do it for a while?
ちょっとする?
Well then, just a little.
じゃあちょっと
This is what it looks like today.
今日は、こんな感じです
Please get together.
集まってもらって
Please get a little closer.
ちょっと密集してもらって
Wow, that's a really bad video.
あんま、なんかいけない映像ですね
It's a little dark.
ちょっと暗いな
That's a bad video, I guess.
いけない映像だね、なんか
Please sit down for a moment.
ちょっとじゃあ座ってもらって
What do you all think of this...
みなさん、どうでしょう、この...
This smells like crime...
犯罪の匂いがする、この...
How about this cute, cute baby?
可愛い可愛い、この子はどうでしょう?
Please enjoy it today.
堪能してください、今日は
Uncle, please touch my breasts.
お じ さんごっぱい触ってろ、こんのいっそ
It's okay.
大丈夫だ
That's enough.
もういいよ
Uncle, please touch my boobs.
おじさんごっぱい触ってろ、こんのいっそ
Then let's start.
じゃあ始まっちゃう
Otsumo from earlier.
さっきのおつつも
Well then, let's turn that one on.
じゃあ、あっちをつけちゃおう
All at once, five people gained broadcast rights.
一気にさ、5人もさ、中継権増えたね
You can update up to 5 people with experience at once.
経験人数も5人も一気に更新できるよ
It's cute.
可愛いね
Show your armpits a little bit, like your armpits.
ちょっと脇も見せて、脇みたいに
Like the armpit.
脇 みたいに
If you can find your hands, show me your butt.
手が見つけたら、ちょっとお尻見せて
Go this way.
こっちに行ってさ
Your butt is too pretty.
お尻きれいすぎだろ
Show your butt.
お尻つき出して
That's amazing, you've got a lot of work to do.
すごいね、いっぱい手あんね
That's amazing, everyone is doing it.
すごいね、みんなしてて
Let's move this chair away.
ちょっとこの椅子どかすよ
Too cute.
可愛すぎ
Um, where did my arm go?
あれ、自分の腕どこいったん?
Where are your hands?
手、どこいったん?
Try spreading it out a little with your own hands.
自分の手でさ、ちょっと広げてみなよ、
this.
これ
From below, yeah yeah yeah.
下から、そうそうそう
Spread it out, yeah yeah yeah.
広げてみな、そうそうそう
Expand it further.
もっと広げな
You taught me the other day.
この間教えたでしょ
Yes, I touched it.
そう、触ったんだ
Beautiful.
綺麗な
With both hands, from the other person, to the friends on the left and right,
両手で、相手からさ、左右の友人とは、
I'm touching my dick.
チンチン触ってるわ
I can see all kinds of things.
いろんなチンチン見えてるんだけど
There may be some things that are different from the norm.
普通と違うやつもあるかもしん
do not have.
ない
Hey, nice.
ちょ いね
Because I was surrounded by everyone.
みんなに囲んだから
Chin, surround it.
チン、囲んで
Looks like it can be done.
できそうだね
And there's chin chin on the front too.
で、正面にもチンチン
Let's go back, let's go back.
バックにしよう、バックに
So, hold it a little bit and break your hand like this.
で、ちょっと持って、こうやって手を壊すんだよ
Are you busy?
忙しいの?
Don't stop this.
止めないで、これ
I'm having trouble with the sound.
音のほうが困ってる
What do you think, baby?
赤ちゃん、どう思う?
Chin Chin in general.
チンチン一般の
Okay?
よし?
I feel like I'm coming here.
なんか、ここに寄っちゃってるね
The window wasn't dry.
窓が乾いてなかったやつだね
Everyone can do this with just one book.
こ っちも一本でみんなができる
Yeah, can you sit down?
うん、うんこ座りできる?
Just sit on your poop and lick my dick.
うんこ座りでちょっと、おチンチン舐めてみて
A little hand and some sweets.
ちょっと手と、お菓子ね
Let me see your face for a moment.
ちょっとお顔させて
I'll go out alone right away.
早速、一人出ちゃう
It feels good, it's delicious.
気持ちいいんだよ、うまいんだよ
It's cute, kind of.
可愛いね、なんか
Even with that static face, she's cute.
あの、静止まみれの顔でも可愛いね
Dick, here comes dick.
チ ンコ、チンコきた、ほら
I feel like I've become spoiled.
なんか もう、甘んできんなみたい
I hate dicks.
チンコ嫌だよ
It's a bit of an odd-shaped dick, isn't it?
ちょっと変わった形のチンコでしょ?
Do you understand?
分かる?
picture?
え?
A famous machine?
名機の?
Is it a famous machine?
名機かな?
Do you understand?
分かる?
Kaizo Chinku?
カイゾーチンク?
Look closely, you haven't seen it before, have you?
よく見て、見たことないでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Because I went with the rough version,
みこすり判でいっちゃったからさ、
Just a little.
ちょっとさ
Please clean up a bit.
ちょっと お掃除してください
Can I go?
行っていい?
Yeah.
うん
A little too much for my teeth.
ちょっと歯によっぱい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
A little out of sight.
ちょっと目抜けて
Mouth, open, mouth.
お口、開けて、お口
Leave it as is.
そのままでよ
I've got a good dick.
ちゃんとチンコ飼えてんだよ
It's going to close, it's going to close, it's going to close.
めっちゃ閉まる、閉まるわ、マジで
I got it.
取れちゃったよ
It's the same with sperm.
精子でそうだわ
Let's get it out, sperm.
出すよ、精子
Kuya!
くや!
I'll give it to you, hon.
出すよ、ほんで
If you have a dick, I'll take it out.
チンコ飼えてるんやもん、出すから
You're cute, Akane-chan.
可愛いよ、アカネちゃん
Akane-chan after being beaten.
やられた後のアカネちゃん
how was it?
どうだった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
fun?
楽しい?
I did a lot of different things.
いっぱい、いろんな、いっぱいいろんなことしたね
It was my first experience.
初 経験したね
Some were big, some were fast,
大きいのもいたし、早いのもいたし、
You took a lot of showers.
いっぱい浴びたね
Am I okay?
私大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫なの?
Why is it okay?
なんで大丈夫なの?